<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Changelog on Dread's Skyrim Build</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/</link><description>Recent content in Changelog on Dread's Skyrim Build</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guide changelog</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/guide-changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/guide-changelog/</guid><description>2021-09-15 Added Locations JK&amp;rsquo;s The Hag&amp;rsquo;s Cure Updated Gameplay Smooth Cam Updated install instructions Models &amp;amp; Textures Embers XD Updated install instructions Patches JK&amp;rsquo;s Interiors Patch Collection Updated install instructions Models &amp;amp; Textures - Grass Fixed a typo that prevented the section from showing up and moved The grass must grow to this section. Removed Models &amp;amp; Textures Inferno 2021-08-20 Updated Patches JK&amp;rsquo;s Interiors Patch Collection Updated install instructions Gameplay SunHelm Updated install instructions Removed Gameplay Disease Descriptions for the Immersive Adventurer SE Models &amp;amp; Textures - Weapons and Armors aMidianBorn Matching Armory - Glass Armor and Weapons Redundant, included in Cathedral Armory Added Locations JK&amp;rsquo;s Arnleif and Sons Trading Company JK&amp;rsquo;s Silver-Blood Inn 2021-08-10 Updated Preparations Updated BethINI settings Updated arguments for Textgen and DynDOLOD Foundation DynDOLOD Resources Updated to v3.</description></item><item><title>Patches changelog</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/patches-changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/patches-changelog/</guid><description>2021-07-11 Patches updated, removed patches for removed mods
2021-06-27 Updated patches to the latest Adamant/Mundus/Aetherius
2021-06-23 Some patches updated with small changes. Many patches moved to the new mod Animated Heavy Armory.
2021-06-04 Patches updated to support DAR version of Animated Armoury.</description></item></channel></rss>