<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gameplay on Dread&#39;s Skyrim Build</title>
    <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gameplay on Dread&#39;s Skyrim Build</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>General</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/general/</guid>
      <description>Better Jumping SE Get the mod   GIST - Genuinely Intelligent Soul Trap SE Get the mod   Download and install the Main File.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI &amp; Combat</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/ai-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/ai-combat/</guid>
      <description>AI Overhaul SSE Get the mod   Archery Gameplay Overhaul SE Get the mod   Install the main file and the nemesis patch. When installing the nemesis patch, make sure to set the folder named Data as data directory. Mod Organizer will show a warning saying that there is no game data on top level. Ignore this warning.
Better Stealth AI for Followers Get the mod   Blade and Blunt Get the mod   Install the main file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping &amp; Survival</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/camping-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/camping-survival/</guid>
      <description>There are two supported survival mods to choose from. If you want to use a survival mod, choose either the official Creation Club Survival Mode or the minimalistic mod The Frozen North.
 Camping Lite (Special Edition) Get the mod   The Frozen North - Minimalistic survival overhaul Get the mod   Do not use this mod if you use Creation Club Survival Mode.
 Install the main file The Frozen North.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classes &amp; Races</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/classes-races/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/classes-races/</guid>
      <description>Aetherius - A Race Overhaul Get the mod   Class Overhaul Re-Imagined (SkyRem - Cori) Get the mod   Experience Get the mod   Do not activate this mod yet. Wait until you have left the first cell of Alternate Start to avoid getting experience when different mods do their initial setup routines.
Manbeast - A Werewolf Overhaul Get the mod   Scion - A Vampire Overhaul Get the mod   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafting</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/crafting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/crafting/</guid>
      <description>Ars Metallica - Smithing Enhancement Get the mod   Crafting Skills Revamped Get the mod   Download the main file and the following optional files:
 Crafting Skills Revamped - Skyrim Skill Uncapper Patch Potions Restore Over Time  More Craftable Equipment Get the mod   Download and install the main file and the optional CBBE file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economy &amp; Item Balance</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/economy-item-balance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/economy-item-balance/</guid>
      <description>Trade and Barter Get the mod   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immersion &amp; Role-Playing</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/immersion-role-playing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/immersion-role-playing/</guid>
      <description>Carriage and Ferry Travel Overhaul Get the mod   Install the main file and the Dawnstar by Arthmoor Patch.
Daedric Voices Get the mod   Install the main file.
Disease Descriptions for the Immersive Adventurer SE Get the mod   Guard Dialogue Overhaul SE Get the mod   High-Level Loot Rarified Get the mod   Install the main file. Select everything in the installer.
Hunters Not Bandits Get the mod   Download and install Hunters Not Bandits for RDO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic &amp; Abilities</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/magic-abilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/magic-abilities/</guid>
      <description>Mundus - A Standing Stone Overhaul Get the mod   Mysticism - A Magic Overhaul Get the mod   Install the main file
Thunderchild - Epic Shouts and Immersion Get the mod   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quests &amp; Stories</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/quests-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/quests-stories/</guid>
      <description>A Lovely Letter Alternate Routes Get the mod   Alternate Start - Live Another Life - SSE Get the mod   Angi&amp;rsquo;s Camp Tweaks Get the mod   The Brotherhood of Old - Open Beta - SSE Get the mod   The Choice is Yours (SE) Get the mod   Clockwork (SSE) Get the mod   Cutting Room Floor Get the mod   Dawnguard and Clan Volkihar Epilogues Get the mod   The Forgotten City Get the mod   Gildergreen Regrown Get the mod   The Gray Cowl of Nocturnal SE Get the mod   The Gray Cowl of Nocturnal SSE - HD pack Get the mod   Gray Cowl of Nocturnal Alikr Flora Overhaul SE Get the mod   Helgen Reborn Get the mod   Here We Go Again - World Interactions Get the mod   Improved College Entry - Questline Tweaks Get the mod   Improved Companions - Questline Tweaks Get the mod   Moon and Star Get the mod   Moonpath to Elsweyr SSE Get the mod   More Radiant Quests for the Companions Get the mod   Choose Option 1 in the installer (suggestion)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills &amp; Perks</title>
      <link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/skills-perks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild_v2/mod-installation/gameplay/skills-perks/</guid>
      <description>Adamant - A Perk Overhaul Get the mod   Install the main file and the optional Adamant Addons - Shrines and Amulets.
If this mod is updated midgame from 3.x to 4.x, use Ish&amp;rsquo;s Respec Mod to reclaim your perk points before updating. Ish&amp;rsquo;s Respec Mod adds a potion to vendors that can be added to your inventory using the console. Use the help command in the console to find the item id for the potion, Draught of Fate Unwound.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
