<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dread's Skyrim Build</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/</link><description>Recent content on Dread's Skyrim Build</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Extenders</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/extenders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/extenders/</guid><description>SKSE64 Download Root Files Installation
Download the most current archive for Skyrim SE. Open the downloaded archive and extract the following files to the Skyrim Special Edition folder: (..\Steam\steamapps\common\Skyrim Special Edition) skse64_X_X_X.dll skse64_loader.exe skse64_steam_loader.dll Data Files Installation
Open MO2 and right-click on the mod list. Hover over All Mods and select Create empty mod. Type in SKSE64, or anything similar. Hold down the Ctrl key and double-click on the newly created mod in the mod list.</description></item><item><title>Guide changelog</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/guide-changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/guide-changelog/</guid><description>2021-06-23 Added Items Skyrim Spear Mechanic SE Animated Heavy Armory User Interface SkyUI Weapons Pack SE Removed Items Heavy Armory Updated Patches JK&amp;rsquo;s Interiors Patch Collection Updated install options Gameplay High-Level Loot Rarified Updated install options 2021-06-10 Added Locations JK&amp;rsquo;s The Ragged Flagon JK&amp;rsquo;s The Pawned Prawn Updated Patches JK&amp;rsquo;s Interiors Patch Collection 2021-06-04 Added Items Animated Armoury - DAR Version - New Weapons with animations Removed Items Animated Armoury - New Weapons with animations 2021-05-24 Added Items Royal Armory Tweaks and Fixes Locations Stendarr Rising - The Hall of the Vigilant Rebuild 2021-05-23 Moved SSE Engine Fixes (moved from Fixes to Resources) Removed Models &amp;amp; Textures aMidianBorn book of silence Creatures (removed optional file from aMidianBorn book of silence.</description></item><item><title>Patches changelog</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/patches-changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/changelog/patches-changelog/</guid><description>2021-06-23 Some patches updated with small changes. Many patches moved to the new mod Animated Heavy Armory.
2021-06-04 Patches updated to support DAR version of Animated Armoury.</description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/resources/</guid><description>.NET Script Framework Download Address Library for SKSE Plugins Download Download and install the All-in-One Main File.
FileAccess Interface for Skyrim SE Scripts - FISSES Download Only the Main File is required.
JContainers SE Download Download and install JContainers SE
PapyrusUtil SE - Modders Scripting Utility Functions Download Scaleform Translation++ Download Skyrim Skill Uncapper Download SkyUI Download SSE Engine Fixes (skse64 plugin) Download Download and install (Part 1) Engine Download (Part 2) Engine Fixes - skse64 Preloader and TBB Lib.</description></item><item><title>Foundation</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/foundation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/foundation/</guid><description>Unofficial High Definition Audio Project Download Download and install all Main Files. Merge when asked.
Unofficial Skyrim Special Edition Patch Download Skyrim Particle Patch for ENB Download Download and install the Special Edition PARTICLE PATCH ALL-IN-ONE INSTALLATION file. Do not install the plugin, it is not needed.
DynDOLOD Resources Download Download and install DynDOLOD Resources SE. Install using the following options:
Whiterun Exterior Solitude Exterior High Hrothgar Window Glow DLC2 Vvardenfell 3D Plume Desync Birds of Prey Static Mesh Improvement Mod Download Choose custom install in the installer and choose the following:</description></item><item><title>Animation &amp; Effects</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/animation-effects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/animation-effects/</guid><description>360 Walk and Run Plus Download In the installer, choose:
Male Male: 360 + cloak Head Direction: Face towards the direction of movement Female Female: 360 + cloak Head Direction: Face towards the direction of movement BBP Option: BBP Off Optional Patch: Choose nothing. Common: 360 swimming D13 Faster GET UP STAND UP Animation Download Install loose files.</description></item><item><title>Models &amp; Textures</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/models-textures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/models-textures/</guid><description>Alpine Forest of Whiterun Valley Download aMidianBorn Book of Silence SE Download Download and install the optional files:
aMidianBorn book of silence_ARMORS
Custom Iron and baded: Iron - Vanilla Cut Steel: Steel Steel Plate: Steel Plate Leather: Leather Hide and Studded: Hide Fur: Fur Elven: Gold Dwarwen: Dwarwen Ancient Nord: Ancient Nord Orcish: Orcish Scaled: Scaled Wolf: Wolf - Grey Fur Glass: Glass - Golden Ebony - Ebony - Black Blades: Blades Falmer: Falmer aMidianBorn book of silence_DRAGONBORN DLC</description></item><item><title>Sounds &amp; Music</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/sounds-music/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/sounds-music/</guid><description>Audio Overhaul for Skyrim SE Download Do not install any patches.
Better Animal Footsteps Download Choose to install all footstep sounds. Do not install any patches.
Better Horse Pain Sounds Download Heart of the Beast - Werewolf Sound and Texture Overhaul Download Recommendation: Feral Werewolf sounds - HIGH AGGRESSION.
IHSS - Improved Horse Step Sounds Download Lower Sounding Thieves Guild Door Download Realistic wolf howls Download Recommendation: Realistic Wolf Howls more barks than howls</description></item><item><title>Creature Skeleton</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/creature-skeleton/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/creature-skeleton/</guid><description>Absolute Arachnophobia Download Astounding Flame Atronachs Download Astonishing Frost Atronachs Download Bristleback Boars Download Bullish Bovine Download Callous Dwemer Centurions Download Dramatic Deer Download Dreaded Dwarven Spiders Download Grandiose Giants Download Grave Gargoyles Download Gritty Goats Download Hardy Hares Download Heartland Horses Download Heinous Ash Hoppers Download Hellish Hounds Download Honored Hounds Download Hulking Horkers Download Immersive Dragons Download Immersive Smilodons Download Infamous Ice Wraiths Download Looming Lurkers Download Marvelous Mudcrabs Download Mighty Mammoths Download Nightmare Chaurus Download Notorious Netches Download Riekling Reavers Download Riekling Roughriders Download Salty Slaughterfish Download Savage Bear Download Sickening Skeevers Download Sinister Spriggans Download Supreme Chaurus Hunters Download Supreme Dwemer Spheres Download Supreme Seekers Download Supreme Vampire Lords Download Install Supreme Vampire Lords XP32 SE</description></item><item><title>Character Appearance</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/character-appearance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/character-appearance/</guid><description>Argonian Improvements SSE - Horns Download Caliente’s Beautiful Bodies Enhancer -CBBE- Download The Nexus page linked above contains NSFW images. No nude options will be used in this guide. If they are forced by the mod, other mods will override the options.
The CBBE body is chosen because of its versatility. Recommended presets makes the body look realistic or vanilla-ish.*
Install the main file and the optional file ‘CBBE ESL-flagged .</description></item><item><title>Fixes</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/fixes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/fixes/</guid><description>1st Person Candlelight Fix Download Archery Quick Shot Perk Bug Fix Download Bug Fixes SSE Download Butterflies Land True Download Butterflies Unchained Download Install esl version
Enchantment Reload Fix SE Download Eye Normal Map Fix SSE Download Install Eye Normal Map Fix SSE BC7
Fixed Dragon Stalking Fix Download Fuz Ro D-oh - Silent Voice Download Install main and optional files.</description></item><item><title>User Interface</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/user-interface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/user-interface/</guid><description>Better Container Controls for SkyUI Download Do not install the main file, install the esl optional file only. If you play with a gamepad, skip this mod completely.
Better Dialogue Controls Download Better MessageBox Controls Download Easy Wheelmenu - SSE Conversion Download Easy Wheelmenu for Nether&amp;rsquo;s Follower Framework Download Font Overhaul - Natural Typefaces for Skyrim Download Immersive HUD - iHUD Special Edition Download Lore-Based Loading Screens (SE) Download MoreHUD Inventory Edition Download MoreHUD SE Download Choose the light master version.</description></item><item><title>Items</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/items/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/items/</guid><description>Armor, Clothing &amp;amp; Accessories Bandolier - Bags and Pouches Classic Download Black Sacrament Armor Download Install Black Sacrament Armour - SSE CBBE BodySlide and Black Sacrament Armour - ESL version. Delete the file BlackSacramentArmor.esp (keep BlackSacramentArmor.esl). Some optional tweaks are available in this guides patches to make this armor less overpowered. Even so, it is still possible to combine armor pieces in a way that should be considered cheating since it applies armor rating twice, for example using a barette, a hood and a cowl.</description></item><item><title>Gameplay</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/gameplay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/gameplay/</guid><description>General Better Jumping SE Download GIST - Genuinely Intelligent Soul Trap SE Download Download and install the Main File.
AI &amp;amp; Combat AI Overhaul SSE Download Archery Gameplay Overhaul SE Download Install the main file and the nemesis patch. When installing the nemesis patch, make sure to set the folder named Data as data directory. Mod Organizer will show a warning saying that there is no game data on top level.</description></item><item><title>New Characters</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/new-characters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/new-characters/</guid><description>Enemies Arena - An Encounter Zone Overhaul Download Deadly Dragons Download Install the main file, choose Loremonger version. Do not choose any optionals.
Install the patches. In the patches installer, choose:
Diverse Dragons and Splendor Dragons Loremonger Do not use the Wyrmstooth patch, a patch is provided in the guide&amp;rsquo;s patches.
Diverse Dragons Collection SE Download OBIS SE - Organized Bandits In Skyrim Special Edition Download Install main file and OBIS SE Patrols addon.</description></item><item><title>Lighting &amp; Weather</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/lighting-weather/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/lighting-weather/</guid><description>Cathedral Weathers and Seasons Download Install the main file.
Cathedral Weathers MCM Download Luminosity Lighting Overhaul - The Cathedral Concept Download Obsidian Mountain Fogs Download Relighting Skyrim - SSE Download Storm Lightning for SSE Download In the installer, choose Skyrim Special Edition and the latest game version. Choose esl flagged plugin. Recommended settings for halo are as follows:</description></item><item><title>Locations</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/locations/</guid><description>New Structures &amp;amp; Landmarks Bells of Skyrim Download In the installer, choose to install the JK&amp;rsquo;s Skyrim patch.
Oblivion Gates Remade Download In the installer, choose map markers and Mountain-Like Textures for MAJESTIC MOUNTAINS.
Solitude Skyway Download Solstheim Lighthouse Download Install Solstheim Lighthouse v1.2 ESL and HD Raven Rock Brick Texture Replacer
Solstheim - Skaal Fishing Camp Download Windhelm Lighthouse Download New Lands Falskaar Download Midwood Isle SE Download Install the main file and the optional Solitude Ship Alternative Location Patch</description></item><item><title>ENB</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/enb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/enb/</guid><description>It is up to you if you want to use an ENB or not. If you already have a problem getting a high enough framerate, you should probably not use an ENB. ENB&amp;rsquo;s enhances visuals, but I do not use one in my own setup. I always find places in the game world where the lightning gets too strong or weak, which puts me off. The game looks good without an ENB.</description></item><item><title>ENB Presets</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/enb-presets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/enb-presets/</guid><description>If you have chosen to use ENB, you are free to use any ENB you want. The following ENB&amp;rsquo;s are supported with tweaks available in the guides patches later. Choose one of the following ENB&amp;rsquo;s (just one for now).
A Cathedralist&amp;rsquo;s ENB Download Download A Cathedralist&amp;rsquo;s ENB or A Cathedralist&amp;rsquo;s ENB - High Quality. Extract the contents of the downloaded archive to the main game folder.</description></item><item><title>Patches</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/patches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/patches/</guid><description>College of Winterhold The Missing Apprentices Quest Fix Download Falskaar - Addons and Patches Download Choose
Bug Fixes Boat Location Patch Fast Travel Addon Unique Region Names Addon JK&amp;rsquo;s Interiors Patch Collection Download Download and install the main file. In the installer, choose the following:
Select JKs Interiors
JK&amp;rsquo;s Angeline&amp;rsquo;s Aromatics JK&amp;rsquo;s Arcadia&amp;rsquo;s Cauldron JK&amp;rsquo;s Banned Mare JK&amp;rsquo;s Bee and Barb JK&amp;rsquo;s Belethor&amp;rsquo;s General Goods JK&amp;rsquo;s Bits and Pieces JK&amp;rsquo;s Blue Palace JK&amp;rsquo;s Candlehearth Hall JK&amp;rsquo;s Dragonreach JK&amp;rsquo;s The Drunken Huntsman JK&amp;rsquo;s Elgrims Elixirs JK&amp;rsquo;s New Gnisis Cornerclub JK&amp;rsquo;s Palace of the Kings JK&amp;rsquo;s Pawned Prawn JK&amp;rsquo;s Radiant Ramient JK&amp;rsquo;s Ragged Flagon JK&amp;rsquo;s Sadri&amp;rsquo;s Used Wares Jk&amp;rsquo;s Sleeping Giant Inn JK&amp;rsquo;s Warmaiden JK&amp;rsquo;s White Phial JK&amp;rsquo;s Winking Skeever JK&amp;rsquo;s Angeline&amp;rsquo;s Aromatics</description></item><item><title>Utilities</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/utilities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/utilities/</guid><description>BodySlide and Outfit Studio Download Download and install as a normal mod.
Instructions to add tool as executable
In Mod Organizer 2, click in the Data tab Right click on CalienteTools\BodySlide\BodySlide x64.exe and choose Add as Executable. A dialog box opens asking for a name of the executable. Accept the default name by clicking OK. To set BodySlide to output data to its output mod:
Run BodySlide x64 through Mod Organizer Click Settings Click Advanced Click Browse to choose the Output Path and browse to the BodySlide _Output folder.</description></item><item><title>LOD generation textures</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/lod-generation-textures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/lod-generation-textures/</guid><description>The mods in this section will be deactivated once LOD has been generated.
Cathedral landscapes LOD generation textures Download Install LODGEN Textures for v3.
Do not merge with the Cathedral landscapes main file that was installed in the Foundational Mods section.
SSE-Terrain-Tamriel Download Download the recommended optional SSE-Terrain-Tamriel.esm listed at the end of the first post. Create an empty mod in Mod Organizer 2 and place the downloaded file inside.</description></item></channel></rss>