<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mod Installation on Dread's Skyrim Build</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/</link><description>Recent content in Mod Installation on Dread's Skyrim Build</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Extenders</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/extenders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/extenders/</guid><description>SKSE64 Download Root Files Installation
Download the most current archive for Skyrim SE. Open the downloaded archive and extract the following files to the Skyrim Special Edition folder: (..\Steam\steamapps\common\Skyrim Special Edition) skse64_X_X_X.dll skse64_loader.exe skse64_steam_loader.dll Data Files Installation
Open MO2 and right-click on the mod list. Hover over All Mods and select Create empty mod. Type in SKSE64, or anything similar. Hold down the Ctrl key and double-click on the newly created mod in the mod list.</description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/resources/</guid><description>Address Library for SKSE Plugins Download Download and install the All-in-One Main File.
FileAccess Interface for Skyrim SE Scripts - FISSES Download Only the Main File is required.
JContainers SE Download Download and install JContainers SE
PapyrusUtil SE - Modders Scripting Utility Functions Download powerofthree&amp;rsquo;s Papyrus Extender Download Install the main file for SSE
Scaleform Translation++ Download Skyrim Skill Uncapper Download SkyUI Download SSE Engine Fixes (skse64 plugin) Download Download and install (Part 1) Engine Download (Part 2) Engine Fixes - skse64 Preloader and TBB Lib.</description></item><item><title>Foundation</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/foundation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/foundation/</guid><description>Unofficial High Definition Audio Project Download Download and install all Main Files. Merge when asked.
Unofficial Skyrim Special Edition Patch Download Skyrim Particle Patch for ENB Download Download and install the Special Edition PARTICLE PATCH ALL-IN-ONE INSTALLATION file. Do not install the plugin, it is not needed.
DynDOLOD Resources 3 Download Download and install DynDOLOD Resources SE 3. Install using the following options:</description></item><item><title>LOD generation textures</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/lod-generation-textures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/lod-generation-textures/</guid><description>The mods in this section will be deactivated once LOD has been generated.
Cathedral landscapes LOD generation textures Download If you intend to use The Grass Must Grow, these LOD generation textures are redundant. If this is the case, do not install this mod
Install LODGEN Textures for v3.
Do not merge with the Cathedral landscapes main file that was installed in the Foundational Mods section.
SSE-Terrain-Tamriel Download Download the recommended optional SSE-Terrain-Tamriel.</description></item><item><title>Animation &amp; Effects</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/animation-effects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/animation-effects/</guid><description>D13 Faster GET UP STAND UP Animation Download Install loose files.
Dynamic Animation Replacer Download EVG Conditional Idles Download Choose full install in the installer. The modular install is also supported.
Immersive Animations Download In the installer choose:
Main Module Sneaking Strafe Greatsword Sprint Rogue Stab Blocking Animation Pack SSE Download Dual Wield Improved Animation SSEImmersive Interactions - Animated Actions Download Immersive Interactions - Animated Actions Download Adds third person animations for several interactions.</description></item><item><title>Lighting &amp; Weather</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/lighting-weather/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/lighting-weather/</guid><description>An alternative to Cathedral Weathers is Azurite Weathers by the same mod author. It works without any patches, just skip Cathedral Weather and use Azurite Weathers instead.
Cathedral Weathers and Seasons Download Install the main file and the unofficial update.
Cathedral Weathers MCM Download Dynamic Volumetric Lighting and Sun Shadows Download Install the main file.
Luminosity Lighting Overhaul - The Cathedral Concept Download Obsidian Mountain Fogs Download Relighting Skyrim - SSE Download Download and install Relighting Skyrim SSE - Exteriors Only</description></item><item><title>Models &amp; Textures</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/models-textures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/models-textures/</guid><description>Alpine Forest of Whiterun Valley Download Arctic - Frost Effects Redux Download Install the main file using the following options:
Resolution: Lite Color: Realistic hue Size: x.5 Style: Standard Plugin option: Frost mesh patch (esl-tagged) Arri&amp;rsquo;s Snow Elf Ruins Retexture Special Edition Download Barenziah&amp;rsquo;s Glory SE Download Recommended install options:
Desaturated Crown Texture - 1k Gamwich Jewelrybox Texture - 1k Gamwich Gem Texture - dark Bellyaches Animal and Creature Pack SSE Download Recommended install options:</description></item><item><title>Models &amp; Textures - Grass</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/model-textures-grass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/model-textures-grass/</guid><description>The grass included in Cathedral Landscapes is very performance friendly, but unfortunately it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look very good when used alongside an ENB with detailed shadows enabled. These mods installs better looking grass that looks good with an ENB preset, but at the cost of performance. If your computer can handle it, installing these mods is recommended whether you use an ENB or not.
Folkvangr - Grass and Landscape Overhaul Download Northern Shores SE Download Download and install Northern Shores 2K.</description></item><item><title>Sounds &amp; Music</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/sounds-music/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/sounds-music/</guid><description>Audio Overhaul for Skyrim SE Download Do not install any patches.
Better Animal Footsteps Download Choose to install all footstep sounds. Do not install any patches.
Better Horse Pain Sounds Download Heart of the Beast - Werewolf Sound and Texture Overhaul Download Recommendation: Feral Werewolf sounds - HIGH AGGRESSION.
IHSS - Improved Horse Step Sounds Download Lower Sounding Thieves Guild Door Download Realistic wolf howls Download Recommendation: Realistic Wolf Howls more barks than howls</description></item><item><title>Creature Skeleton</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/creature-skeleton/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/creature-skeleton/</guid><description>Absolute Arachnophobia Download Astounding Flame Atronachs Download Astonishing Frost Atronachs Download Bristleback Boars Download Bullish Bovine Download Callous Dwemer Centurions Download Dramatic Deer Download Dreaded Dwarven Spiders Download Grandiose Giants Download Grave Gargoyles Download Gritty Goats Download Hardy Hares Download Heartland Horses Download Heinous Ash Hoppers Download Hellish Hounds Download Honored Hounds Download Hulking Horkers Download Immersive Dragons Download Immersive Smilodons Download Infamous Ice Wraiths Download Looming Lurkers Download Marvelous Mudcrabs Download Mighty Mammoths Download Nightmare Chaurus Download Notorious Netches Download Riekling Reavers Download Riekling Roughriders Download Salty Slaughterfish Download Savage Bear Download Sickening Skeevers Download Sinister Spriggans Download Supreme Chaurus Hunters Download Supreme Dwemer Spheres Download Supreme Seekers Download Supreme Vampire Lords Download Install Supreme Vampire Lords XP32 SE</description></item><item><title>Character Appearance</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/character-appearance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/character-appearance/</guid><description>Argonian Improvements SSE - Horns Download Caliente’s Beautiful Bodies Enhancer -CBBE- Download The Nexus page linked above contains NSFW images. No nude options will be used in this guide. If they are forced by the mod, other mods will override the options.
Some armor textures featured in the guide is not compatible with CBBE. Using CBBE is not recommended for this reason but is still supported for those users that want to use it.</description></item><item><title>Fixes</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/fixes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/fixes/</guid><description>1st Person Candlelight Fix Download Do not install if you use ENB Light.
Archery Quick Shot Perk Bug Fix Download Bug Fixes SSE Download Butterflies Land True Download Butterflies Unchained Download Install esl version
Enchantment Reload Fix SE Download Eye Normal Map Fix SSE Download Install Eye Normal Map Fix SSE BC7
Fixed Dragon Stalking Fix Download Fuz Ro D-oh - Silent Voice Download Install main and optional files.</description></item><item><title>User Interface</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/user-interface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/user-interface/</guid><description>Better Container Controls for SkyUI Download Do not install the main file, install the esl optional file only. If you play with a gamepad, skip this mod completely.
Better Dialogue Controls Download Better MessageBox Controls Download Easy Wheelmenu - SSE Conversion Download Easy Wheelmenu for Nether&amp;rsquo;s Follower Framework Download Font Overhaul - Natural Typefaces for Skyrim Download Use the following install instructions:</description></item><item><title>Items</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/items/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/items/</guid><description>Armor, Clothing &amp;amp; Accessories Bandolier - Bags and Pouches Classic Download Black Sacrament Armor Download Install Black Sacrament Armour SSE. CBBE users installs Black Sacrament Armour - SSE CBBE BodySlide instead. Install Black Sacrament Armour - ESL version. Delete the file BlackSacramentArmor.esp (keep BlackSacramentArmor.esl). Some optional tweaks are available in this guides patches to make this armor less overpowered. Even so, it is still possible to combine armor pieces in a way that should be considered cheating since it applies armor rating twice, for example using a barette, a hood and a cowl.</description></item><item><title>Models &amp; Textures - Weapons and Armors</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/models-textures-weapons-and-armors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/models-textures-weapons-and-armors/</guid><description>RUSTIC ARMOR and WEAPONS SE Download Recommendation: 2K
Armor Mesh Fixes SE Download Download and install the main file and the update file.
Cathedral - Armory Download Download and install the main file and the Armor Mesh Fixes SE Patch. CBBE users installs the CBBE BodySlide Patch.
aMidianBorn stormcloak officer armour Download Dragon Masks Retextured SE (4K - 2K) Download Recommendation: 2K</description></item><item><title>Gameplay</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/gameplay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/gameplay/</guid><description>General Better Jumping SE Download GIST - Genuinely Intelligent Soul Trap SE Download Download and install the Main File.
Improvement Names Customized SSE Download SmoothCam Download In the installer, choose SmoothCam AVX and esl.
True Directional Movement - Modernized Third Person Gameplay Download AI &amp;amp; Combat AI Overhaul SSE Download Better Stealth AI for Followers Download Blade and Blunt Download Install the main file and the Blade and Blunt - Timed Block Module file.</description></item><item><title>New Characters</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/new-characters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/new-characters/</guid><description>Enemies Arena - An Encounter Zone Overhaul Download Dragon War - A Dragon Overhaul Download Install the main file and the optional file. In the installer, choose patches for:
Audio Overhaul Skyrim Deadly Spell Impacts Wyrmstooth OBIS SE - Organized Bandits In Skyrim Special Edition Download Install main file and OBIS SE Patrols addon.
Neutral DIVERSE SKYRIM SSE Download Immersive College NPCs Download Use the default settings in the installer.</description></item><item><title>Locations</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/locations/</guid><description>New Structures &amp;amp; Landmarks Bells of Skyrim Download In the installer, choose to install the JK&amp;rsquo;s Skyrim patch.
Oblivion Gates Remade Download In the installer, choose map markers and Mountain-Like Textures for MAJESTIC MOUNTAINS.
Solitude Skyway Download Solstheim Lighthouse Download Install Solstheim Lighthouse v1.2 ESL and HD Raven Rock Brick Texture Replacer
Solstheim - Skaal Fishing Camp Download Windhelm Lighthouse Download New Lands Falskaar Download Midwood Isle SE Download Install the main file and the optional Solitude Ship Alternative Location Patch</description></item><item><title>ENB</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/enb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/enb/</guid><description>It is up to you if you want to use an ENB or not. If you already have a problem getting a high enough framerate, you should probably not use an ENB.
ENB Download Download the latest version by clicking on the version number in the lower left side of the screen. This open a new page that has the download link on the bottom.
Open the downloaded archive and extract the files &amp;lsquo;d3d11.</description></item><item><title>ENB Presets</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/enb-presets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/enb-presets/</guid><description>If you have chosen to use ENB, you are free to use any ENB you want. The following ENB&amp;rsquo;s are recommended. Manually extract the content of the downloaded files to Skyrim&amp;rsquo;s main directory.
The Truth ENB Download To download this ENB you need to register on the site where it is hosted.
ENB for Azurite Weathers Download This ENB is based on The Truth by Phinix and is edited for Azurite Weathers by Mechanicalpanda.</description></item><item><title>Patches</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/patches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/patches/</guid><description>College of Winterhold The Missing Apprentices Quest Fix Download Falskaar - Addons and Patches Download Choose
Bug Fixes Boat Location Patch Fast Travel Addon Unique Region Names Addon JK&amp;rsquo;s Interiors Patch Collection Download Download and install the main file. In the installer, choose the default options. The installer should automatically pick all correct options.
JS Dragon Claws - Patches Download Install:</description></item><item><title>Utilities</title><link>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/utilities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dreadflopp.github.io/dreadsskyrimbuild/mod-installation/utilities/</guid><description>BodySlide and Outfit Studio Download Download and install as a normal mod.
Instructions to add tool as executable
In Mod Organizer 2, click in the Data tab Right click on CalienteTools\BodySlide\BodySlide x64.exe and choose Add as Executable. A dialog box opens asking for a name of the executable. Accept the default name by clicking OK. To set BodySlide to output data to its output mod:
Run BodySlide x64 through Mod Organizer Click Settings Click Advanced Click Browse to choose the Output Path and browse to the BodySlide _Output folder.</description></item></channel></rss>